austar.com.au 2012-12-31

# Privacy Statement - Foxtel provided by AUSTAR

## Foxtel cares about your privacy

We appreciate that your privacy is important to you. Foxtel will continue to protect the personal information you entrust to us.

Foxtel has compiled this page to advise you of how your personal information is handled including how it collects, holds, uses and discloses that information through any interaction you have with Foxtel.

If you are a Foxtel Customer in an area serviced by AUSTAR, this Privacy Statement should be read in conjunction with your Foxtel Customer Agreement by AUSTAR. Foxtel includes Foxtel Management Pty Ltd and its business partners (being Telstra Corporation Limited, the News Corporation Limited and Consolidated Media Holdings, Foxtel Partnership and Telstra Pay TV Pty Limited), Foxtel Cable Television Pty Ltd and Customer Services Pty Ltd and their agents and contractors.

## National Privacy Principles

Foxtel is committed to protecting your personal information. We comply with the National Privacy Principles (NPPs) set out in the Privacy Act 1988. The NPPs regulate the way that organisations can collect, use, keep secure and disclose personal information. It also gives individuals the right to know what information an organisation holds about them and a right to correct that information if it is wrong.

## What information do we collect and why?

The type of information we collect from you will depend on what products and services you use. Generally we collect personal information directly from you, for example when you subscribe to a Foxtel service over the telephone. We may collect personal information about you from a third party for the purpose of marketing our products and services. When you browse this website, we do not collect your personal information. Sometimes, we collect personal information that you choose to give us via online forms or by email, for example when you ask to be on an email list. We only use personal information collected via our website for the purposes for which it was given to us.

When you set up a Foxtel account or become a Foxtel customer you will need to provide certain details so that we can establish and manage your customer account. This includes information such as your name, contact details and information for identification purposes. Foxtel may also request your credit card or bank account details and information to help us assess your credit application where this is relevant. We may also require information about your premises in order to assist with the installation of Foxtel’s services.

Foxtel may offer third party products or services and we may collect information about you in order to provide you with the products, services or information requested.

## Use of information

Foxtel may use your information for purposes which you would reasonably expect, such as managing your account, billing, contacting you (including about your Equipment or to confirm any instructions that you give to us) or providing customer support. Foxtel also collects and uses information about your use of our services for monitoring and evaluation purposes so that we can improve and enhance our products and services.

Foxtel may use your information to notify you about new services or promotions from time to time. If at any stage you no longer wish to receive these communications from Foxtel you can contact us to let us know.

## What information do we disclose?

We may disclose information where you would reasonably expect us to do so, when you have consented or where the disclosure is for an activity related to the purpose for which your information was collected. For example, Foxtel may provide your information to organisations associated with the provision of Foxtel’s services, such as TV channel providers, for marketing and analysis purposes.

Foxtel may disclose your personal information to a credit reporting agency for the purpose of assessing your credit application and maintaining a credit information file about you. The disclosures will include information relating to your credit application including identifying information about you, the fact you have applied for credit (and the amount). We may also subsequently disclose information about your credit relationship with us to a credit reporting agency.

Foxtel may disclose your personal information to government agencies for the purpose of investigating and resolving disputes or complaints concerning your use of our services. Foxtel will not disclose your personal information to any third parties, other than those who are contracted to us to keep the information confidential. We use contractors to perform certain services on our behalf, for example the installation and servicing of Equipment, customer service support, sales activities, and for mailing purposes.

There may be some exceptional circumstances for disclosing your information, such as when there are grounds to believe that the disclosure is necessary to prevent a threat to life or health, or for law enforcement purposes.

## Security and quality of your information

We take all reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we collect, use or disclose is accurate, complete, up-to-date and stored securely.

## How you can access your personal information

You are entitled to access personal information Foxtel holds about you and to amend that information if it is incorrect. To do this, please contact us and include your account details.

## Complaints about breaches of privacy

If you believe that your privacy has been breached by Foxtel, you can lodge a complaint by writing to the address noted below and all attempts will be made to resolve the matter.

If you are not satisfied with the outcome you may refer the matter to the Privacy Commissioner's Office.

Office of the Federal Privacy Commissioner  
**Telephone:** 1300 363 992  
**Email address:** [privacy@privacy.gov.au](mailto:privacy@privacy.gov.au)

**Foxtel customer service contact details**

Foxtel  
Privacy  
Locked Bag 2000  
Gold Coast Mail Centre 9726

**Email address:** [privacy@austar.com.au](mailto:privacy@austar.com.au)  
**Telephone:** 131 999  
**Website:** www.austar.com.au

Your Foxtel service is provided by AUSTAR Entertainment Pty Ltd ABN 93 068 104 530

For details on the use of information gathered on the Foxtel network, please refer to the Foxtel Portal Terms of Use.
